devmate.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy | DevMate

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") is adopted by DevMate, Inc. ("we", or "us") and provides you with the information about what type of information is gathered by www.devmate.com ("Site") and how we collect, use, protect, share, and disclose such information.

This Policy is an integral part of the Site and the Service, as defined below. The privacy practices set forth herein have been established to provide the best services while protecting personal information. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy in whole, you must not use the Site or any services, software, or applications from the Site.

If you have questions or feedback regarding this Policy or any other privacy or security concern, please contact us at support@devmate.com or call +1 (877) 5-MACPAW.

## 1\. Definitions

Unless the context clearly indicates otherwise, the following terms have the following meanings when used in this Policy:

  * **"Service"** means DevMate, the development and distribution assistance platform for software developers. 
  * **"Developer"** means a software development company or developer that has purchased or licensed the Service. 
  * **"Developer Information"** means any data or information provided to or collected by the Service from a Developer. 
  * **"End User"** means the end user of a Developer’s application. 
  * **"User Data"** means data concerning the characteristics and behaviors of the End User. 
  * **"Visitor"** means any person who visits the Site. 

**Please note: the Site and the Service collect different types of information and use such information in different ways, as further described in this Policy.**

## 2\. Information Collected by the Site

As a Visitor to and in connection with your activities with us and on the Site, we may collect certain personal information from you, including, but not limited to:

  * Payment or financial account information;
  * Contact and billing information (including name, email address, postal address, and phone number);
  * Date of birth;
  * Geolocation data;
  * Other personal information you provide to us on the Site or when you interact with us in other ways online and/or offline.

In addition to the above, we or companies acting on our behalf may collect certain computer and browser information through automated technologies such as cookies and web beacons when you visit the Site. The information collected using these tools may include, but is not limited to, your IP address, browser characteristics, operating system, the address of the web page that referred you to the Site, dates and times of Site visits, the language your system uses, and the country and time zone in which your device is located. These automated technologies may also permit the collection of "clickstream data", which may include a log of content you access while browsing the Site.

Companies acting on our behalf may combine the information collected from your visit to the Site with other information they have previously collected. Your web browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict, reject, or disable certain cookies.

We do not seek nor will we knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13.

## 3\. Information Collected by the Service

The Service may collect certain User Data on behalf of the Developer, including, but not limited to: User IP addresses, OS version, OS localization, version of the application, localization of the application, device, bug reports, etc. Upon End User's approval, the Service may also receive additional User Data, such as name, address, e-mail address & other information, from the e-commerce provider. The Service does not collect any personally identifiable information User Data from End User's computers without prior approval by End Users.

ALL PERSONAL USER DATA AND OTHER PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT THE END USERS COLLECTED BY THE SERVICE FOR THE DEVELOPER BELONGS TO THE DEVELOPER. The Developer must comply with all applicable privacy laws or regulations and must maintain a separate privacy policy for the Developer's applications that complies with such laws. Developer Information belongs to us.

## 4\. How We Use the Information We Collect

When we receive personal information from you, we may use it for a number of purposes, including to:

  * Process, manage, complete, and account for transactions;
  * Provide services requested by the Visitor or Developer;
  * Invite you to participate in customer research;
  * Notify you about new products, services, features, promotions, events and special offerings relating to our business we think you will find valuable;
  * Provide customer support and respond to your requests, comments and inquiries;
  * Create and manage online accounts you establish;
  * Verify your identity in certain instances (such as when you pay by check, return merchandise, or request a refund);
  * Protect against, identify and help prevent fraud, unauthorized activity, claims and other liabilities and minimize credit risk;
  * Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, industry standards, our policies, and our terms of use;
  * Operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services, managing our communications, performing market research, and administering the Site).

We will not use your email address for any third party advertisements or notices. If we decide to provide you with email offers, you will have the opportunity to opt-out of any emails by notifying the Company via email at support@devmate.com or by calling+1 (877) 5-MACPAW.

If you send us a request, question, or comment (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), the Company reserves the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users of the Site and the Service.

## 5\. Developer Information

The Company may display the following information to logged-in users according to the access level, if they are owner, developer or team member of an app: First name and last name of all team members, number of activations of the app or version, numbers of downloads, installations, updates of the app or version, crash logs, launch reports, end user data and sales reports, user feedback and exceptions. The Company is not responsible for securing data or information by logged-in users. In no event the Company, its subsidiaries, affiliates or any of their respective directors, officers, employees or agents, shall be liable to products/applications users for revealing information by the logged-in users after obtaining such information by them from the Company.

## 6\. Information We Share

We may share certain personal information we collect about you with partners or third parties who perform services for us or with whom we contract for the purposes described in this policy. For example, we may use third parties to host the Site, operate certain of its features, send e-mails, print or send mailings, conduct customer research, and manage and analyze data and our advertising effectiveness. Such third-party service providers are given the information that they need to perform their designated functions and we do not authorize them to use or disclose your personal information for their own or any others' marketing purposes. Some of these third parties may be located outside your home country, and you acknowledge and agree to that.

If we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, Developer and Visitor information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge and agree that such transfers may occur, and that your personal information can be used by any third party in accordance with this Policy.

## 7\. How We Protect Your Information

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect against loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of information we collect, including the use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption of data. We will not sell or rent your personal information.

## 8\. Legal Disclaimer

We may share the information you provide (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) with law enforcement authorities, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent harm or loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.

## 9\. Links/Affiliated Websites

This Site may contain links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us, including, but not limited to our partners, affiliates and advertisers. This Policy applies only to the Site and the Service, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other website that may be linked to by or in the Site or the Service. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

## 10\. Modification of Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time. Any modifications made will be posted on the Site. Please review the Policy frequently.

The effective date of this Policy is: September 1, 2014.
